IMRAN ADEREMI

Imran.a.aderemi@gmail.com | https://inkedin.com/in/ImranAderemi | https://github.com/ImranAderemi | imranaderemi.co.uk

PERSONAL SUMMARY

I'm an 18-year-old aspiring **Software Developer**, seeking opportunities to gain work experience and learn valuable skills in a professional workplace setting. I'm extremely **goal-driven**, **hardworking**, **determined**, and **eager to learn**. I also have experience using **JavaScript**, **HTML5**, **CSS**, **C++**, **C#**, **MySQL**, **Python**, and **APIs**.

TECHNOLOGIES/SKILLS

Vue.js (JavaScript), HTML5, CSS, C++, C#, MySQL, Python, and APIs.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

1 SEP 2024 - 31 OCT 2024

INTERN SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, INTELLIGENT TECH CONSULTING

I was working as an Intern Software Developer at Intelligent Tech Consulting. As part of my role, I'm being taught how to properly make use of available tools that can help me improve the quality of work I produce, such as **AI** and **Stack Overflow.**

11 MAR 2024 - 28 MAR 2024

INTERN WEB DEVELOPER, 21K DIGITAL MEDIA

A 2-week work placement with 21K Digital media, Where I focused on further developing my skills with **HTML**, **CSS**, and **JavaScript**. I worked on developing webpages for clients and assisted in translating the clients' requirements and brief to the team developing the product.

20 MAR 2023 - 31 MAR 2023

JUNIOR GAMES DEVELOPER, METROCALK

A 2-week placement where I practiced and developed my games development skills using Unreal Engine 4 and Unreal Engine 5. I spent time creating levels and mini projects and practiced exploiting the features that were available.

EDUCATION

SEP 2022 – JUL 2024

B-TEC, WESTMINSTER KINGSWAY COLLEGE, LONDON, ENG

A 2-year course at Westminster Kingsway College where I graduated with an 'MMM' on a Level 3 National Extended Diploma in Information Technology.

SEP 2017 - AUG 2022

GCSES, WESTMINSTER CITY SCHOOL, LONDON, ENG

I attended Westminster City School for 5 years and departed with 8 GCSEs all grade (9-4), Including **Computer Science**, Combined Sciences, English Language, English Literature and Maths.

AWARDS

November 2024

- Responsive Web Design Certification, FREECODECAMP

September 2024

- Foundational C# Certification, MICROSOFT/FREECODECAMP

January 2020

- Certificate of Distinction, UK Bebras Challenge 2020